(train honking)
(train rumbling)
♪ All my girls at the
party, look at that body ♪
♪ Shakin' that thing
like you never did see ♪
♪ Got a nice package all right ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna have
to ride it tonight ♪
♪ All my girls at the
party, look at that body ♪
♪ Shakin' that thing
like you never did see ♪
♪ Got a nice package
all right, edit ♪
♪ Four, three, two, one ♪
(funky music)
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ If you really want it ♪
♪ If you say you need it ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ If you gotta have it ♪
♪ It's all for you
if you make a move ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ I see you staring out
the corner of my eye ♪
♪ You seem uneasy, want to
approach me, throw me a line ♪
♪ But then something inside
you grabs you says who am I ♪
♪ I know exactly 'cause it
happens with all the guys ♪
♪ So you so what you gonna do ♪
♪ Come on and talk to me ♪
♪ Promise you won't
even have an attitude ♪
♪ I'll let you sit
right next to me ♪
♪ Don't join the list
with the other fools ♪
♪ That ain't the way to be ♪
♪ Yes, it's cool,
yes, I'm in the mood ♪
♪ Intimidation got that mind ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ If you really want it ♪
♪ If you say you need it ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ If you gotta have it ♪
♪ It's all for you
if you make a move ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ Can't be afraid or keep
me waiting for too long ♪
♪ Before you know it I'll be
outta here, I'll be gone ♪
♪ Don't try to be all
clever, cute, or even sly ♪
♪ Don't have to work that hard ♪
♪ Just be yourself and
let that be your guide ♪
♪ So you so what you gonna do ♪
♪ So come on talk to me boy ♪
♪ Promise you won't
even have an attitude ♪
♪ I'll even let you
sit right next to me ♪
♪ Don't join the list
with the other fools ♪
♪ That ain't the way to be boy ♪
♪ Yes, it's cool,
yes, I'm in the mood ♪
♪ Intimidation every time ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ If you really want it ♪
♪ If you say you need it ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ Say it again, baby ♪
♪ If you gotta have it ♪
♪ It's all for you
if you make a move ♪
♪ I wanna rock you, baby ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ Tell me I'm the only one ♪
♪ Soon you'll be having fun ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ Come over here
and getcha some ♪
♪ It's all for you
if you make a move ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ All my girls at the
party, look at that body ♪
♪ Shakin' that thing
like you never did see ♪
♪ Got a nice package all right ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna have
to ride it tonight ♪
♪ All my girls at the
party look at that body ♪
♪ Shakin' that thing,
like you never did see ♪
♪ Got a nice package all right ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna have to
ride it tonight, tonight ♪
(dramatic energetic music)
(dramatic funky music)
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ If you really want it ♪
♪ If you say you need it ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ If you gotta have it ♪
♪ It's all for you
if you make a move ♪
♪ It's all for you ♪
♪ All my girls at the
party, look at that body ♪
♪ Shakin' that thing
like you never did see ♪
♪ Got a nice package all
right, it's all for you ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna have
to ride it tonight ♪
♪ All my girls at the
party, look at that body ♪
♪ Shakin' that thing
like you never did see ♪
♪ Got a nice package all right ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna have
to ride it tonight ♪
♪ It's all for you, baby ♪
♪ Tell me I'm the only one ♪
♪ Soon you'll be having
fun, having fun ♪
♪ Come over here and get some ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah, get some ♪
♪ Soon we'll be having fun ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna
have to ride it ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna have
to ride it tonight ♪
♪ Guess I'm gonna
have to ride it ♪
♪♪♪
(car horn beeping)